One of the quotes from talks you've given, you say,
when you talk about art being scary,
you say anything that makes you stand out,
makes you vulnerable.
And yet, this very effort to say, and yet,
I am here, and I'm going to do this.
And this particular image, it's just the fact
that there is this, you know,
carceral formation of men, white men,
in this image that is like,
it feels like such a win because of the beauty
that's captured in the movement, literally,
in this piece against that backdrop.
Would you read this one to us and maybe describe it visually?
Do you care?
It says, Southern Transresistence is beautiful
by Mickey Bradford against a red background.
And there are three white cops.
And in between them is a young, black trans woman
who's voguing in a loral little dress.
And in the foreground are the adoring
hands and raised fists of the community protesters.
OK, and is the cop fiddling with his ring?
I know.
That is so funny.
Literally in the photo, he looks like he's
anxiously fondling his wedding ring.
Yeah, I mean, this is really just an example
of rapid response art because the week that this happened,
you know, I already was doing this project.
I was in touch with Mickey as an organizer at Song.
We had worked together before we knew about each other's work.
I can't remember the piece of legislation
that passed right now, but it was some anti-trans and queer
legislation that was being passed.
And so there was a protest in front of the,
I believe, the governor's house.
And, you know, they'd just been out there for hours
and finally, you know, not even thinking, oh, this would
be a medium moment.
Like truly, I think, just out of organizing, like,
how can I keep our people energized?
Mickey, who's also a vogueer, just started voguing
in front of the police.
And then it got picked up by the media so much.
And so, and so because we already in touch,
we were able to basically create this overnight.
And release it when there was still media
and public attention.
And just the interplay, I mean, this is the case
with so much of my work, between current events,
rapid response art, social media and the internet,
and action on the ground.
And it's a feedback loop.